Guide to the University of Chicago Library. John Crerar Library. Records 1977-2009
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Missing Books Information
  - Missing Books – Servetus, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Missing Books – Shujin, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Missing Books – Siebold, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Missing Books – Simpson, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Missing Books – Sinhalese, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Missing Books – Sloane, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Missing Books – Societas Academiae Scientiarum, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Missing Books – Spachius, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Missing Books – Spallanzani, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Missing Books – Sprogel, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Missing Books – Stahl, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Missing Books – Starkey, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Missing Books – Steensen, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Missing Books – Stevens, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Missing Books – Stoll, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Missing Books – Stridbeck, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Missing Books – Summerside, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Missing Books – Tagalaut, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Missing Books – Thurneisser, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Missing Books – Tib I Yoosuf, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Missing Books – Tissot, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Missing Books – Torrella, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Missing Books – Triller, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Missing Books – Trnka, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Missing Books – True way, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Missing Books – Turner, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Missing Books – Ubaldi, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Missing Books – Valleriola, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Missing Books – Valles, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Missing Books – Valverde, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Missing Books – Varignon, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Missing Books – Verheiden, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Missing Books – Vesalius, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Missing Books – Victoricus, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Missing Books – Victoriis, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Missing Books – Villanova, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Missing Books – Virchow, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Missing Books – Walker, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Missing Books – Wall, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Missing Books – Walther, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Missing Books – Warder, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Missing Books – Waters, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Missing Books – Watkins, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Missing Books – Way to Health, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - Missing Books – Weidemann, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - Missing Books – West, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Missing Books – Wetmore, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - Missing Books – Williamson, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 63)
  - Missing Books – Willis, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 64)
  - Missing Books – Wilson, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 65)
  - Missing Books – Wolley, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 66)
  - Missing Books – Wright, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 67)
  - Missing Books – Wurzburg Universitat, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 68)
  - Missing Books – Yoshitoyo, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 69)
  - Missing Books – Young, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 70)
  - Missing Books – Ziedler, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 71)
- Series III: Audio-Visual
  - Compact Disc 1 & 2 – Kathleen A. Zar Symposium, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Series IV: Oversized
  - Construction – Materials and Products – 3M Book Detection System –Drawings, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Fireshutters – Drawings, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Toilet Accessories – Drawings 1983 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Andrew McCann Lawn Sprinkler Company – Drawings, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Dwyer Products Company – Drawings, 1983-1985 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Esko & Young Inc. – Roofing Drawings, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Forest Security Services – Drawings, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Harding and Cogswell – Soffit Plan, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Montgomery Elevator Company – Drawings, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Schmidt Iron Works – Rolling Doors Drawing, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Construction – Scheduling – Building Schedule, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Interior and Exterior Signage, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Accurate Partitions Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Commonwealth Edison, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Engineering Erection Company Inc., 1982-1985 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Hugh Stubbins & Associates, Inc. – Floor Plans, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Reports – Site Survey Plans, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Revolving Door Diagrams, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Alcan United Concrete – Tunnel Blueprints, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Commonwealth Edison, 1982-1984 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Construction Specialties Inc, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Harding and Cogswell - Drawings and Diagrams, 1982-1984 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Premier Electric Company – Drawings, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Schmidt Iron Works, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Thatcher Engineering Plans, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Woodwork Corporation – Diagrams, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – 3M Book Detection System –Drawings, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Acoustics – Drawings, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Dock Lifts – Drawings, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Fan Housing Drawings, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Fire Protection Drawings, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – General Electric Equipment, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Construction – Sequence and Scheduling Diagram, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Construction – Plans – Building Plans – Commonwealth Edison, 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Plans – Building Plans – Custom Enclosures, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Plans – Building Plans – Holabird and Roche Architect Floorplans, c.1985-195 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Plans – Building Plans – Space Control Corp., 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Plans – Library Bureau Floor Plans and Diagrams, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Plans – Air Handling System Blueprints, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Plans – Dewatering Plan, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Plans – Glass Rails Plan, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Plans – Signage Plans, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Construction – Plans – Ventilation Plans, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Construction – Plans – Water Piping Plan, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Construction – Miscellaneous Sketches and Diagrams, 1983-1984 [1/3] (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Construction – Miscellaneous Sketches and Diagrams, 1983-1984 [2/3] (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Construction – Miscellaneous Sketches and Diagrams, 1983-1984 [3/3] (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Plaque – John Crerar Library Directors Office, n.d. (Box 33)
  - Scrapbook – Photos of Crerar Library, n.d. (Box 33A)
- Series V: Restricted
  - Theft File, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 1)